Starting at university or college can be a big challenge, especially if you’re living away from home for the first time.
开始大学生活可能是一个巨大的挑战，尤其是当你第一次离家居住时。
You're faced with big questions such as, ‘Who's going to do my washing?’
你会面临诸如“谁来帮我洗衣服？”
‘Who's going to tidy my room?’
“谁来整理我的房间？”
And, most importantly, ‘How am I going to eat?’
以及最重要的“我该怎么吃饭？”等大问题。
Yes, living on your own means you have to cook for yourself, and when you're living a student lifestyle, this could be a recipe for disaster.
是的，独立生活意味着你必须自己做饭，而当你过着学生生活时，这可能会成为灾难的根源。
Students, in the UK at least, often rely on staples such as baked beans or cheese on toast.
至少在英国，学生们经常依赖如烤豆子或烤面包配奶酪之类的主食。
And for the more adventurous, there's 'spag bol’ – spaghetti bolognaise - a budget-friendly bowl of minced beef cooked in a tomato sauce, served on a bed of spaghetti.
而对于更爱冒险的学生，还有“spag bol”——博洛尼亚意大利面，这是一碗经济实惠的意大利面，上面配有碎牛肉配番茄酱。
If you make a huge pan of it, you can probably make it last a whole week!
如果你煮一大锅，可能够吃一整个星期！
Other low-cost options include jar sauces and oven pizzas.
其他低成本选择包括罐装酱料和烤箱披萨。
Recently, a British supermarket suggested that rose harissa paste, organic cider vinegar and Swiss bouillon powder were the essential ingredients needed for the 'student store cupboard'.
最近，一家英国超市提出，玫瑰哈里萨辣椒酱、有机苹果醋和瑞士肉汤粉是“学生储藏柜”的必备食材。
But are these items considered essential and affordable for someone on a budget?
但对于预算有限的人来说，这些东西真的算是必需品且价格实惠吗？
Catrin Stewart is 20 and in her final year at the University of Manchester and is currently food editor of the student paper.
卡特琳・斯图尔特今年20岁，这也是她在曼彻斯特大学的最后一年，目前是学生报纸的美食编辑。
She told BBC News that "I'm in a unique position…
她告诉BBC新闻：“我现在的出境极为少见……
I'm in a house of eight people and six are vegan.
我和八个人同住，其中六人是纯素食主义者。
We have to be quite inventive with our food. We have lots of Asian influences, lots of experimenting."
我们必须在饮食上很有创意，很多亚洲风味，很多尝试。”
Another student, Eleanor, is vegetarian and finds this meat-free food "easier and less expensive".
另一名学生埃莉诺是素食主义者，她发现这种无肉食物“更简单、更便宜”。
Living on a limited budget is certainly one obstacle to eating a well-balanced diet – some young people also have limited culinary expertise and besides, there are more fun things to go and do than stay at home and cook, that's why many students survive on takeaways and microwave meals.
预算有限无疑是均衡饮食的一大障碍——一些年轻人的烹饪技能也有限，此外，有更多有趣的事情可以做，而不是待在家里做饭，这就是为什么许多学生靠外卖和微波炉食品度日。
But what should a health-conscious student really have in his or her food cupboard?
但一个注重健康的学生的食品柜里究竟应该有什么呢？
Jack Monroe, a food writer and campaigner, has some advice: baked beans, stuffing, lemon juice, tinned tomatoes and tomato ketchup, described as "salt, sugar, vinegar and tomato all in one handy squeezy bottle."
美食作家兼活动家杰克・梦露有一些建议：烤豆子、馅料、柠檬汁、罐装番茄和番茄酱，他形容番茄酱是“盐、糖、醋和番茄都装在一个方便挤压的瓶子里”。
And if that doesn't appeal, you can always wait until you visit mum and dad for a slap-up meal!
如果这还不够吸引人，你总可以等到去看望父母时美餐一顿！